http://www.rfdtv.com/story/41593148/privacy-policy-r20200121a

NewsWeatherShowsSchedulePeopleLifestyleWatchStreaming + On DemandFind Us on TVListenShop SearchGOGeneral001Privacy PolicyTuesday, January 21st 2020, 5:05 PM CSTUpdated: Wednesday, January 22nd 2020, 3:49 PM CSTLast updated on March 2, 2020 This Privacy Statement describes how Rural Media Group, Inc. (“RMG”) manages personal information and respects your privacy. This policy may be amended from time to time. We encourage visitors to and users of our sites to regularly review our Privacy Policy. All "Personal Information” (which is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. To update your information and preferences, see the section entitled "Updating Your Personal Information and Privacy Preferences." When we refer to “RMG”, we mean the Rural Media Group, Inc. entity that acts as the controller or processor of your information, as explained in more detail in the "Entities Collecting Personal Information" section below. ENTITIES COLLECTING PERSONAL INFORMATION RMG is made up of different legal entities. This privacy notice is issued on behalf of the RMG group of companies so when we mention “RMG”, "we", "us" or "our" in this privacy notice, we are referring to the relevant company in RMG responsible for processing your data. The applicable Terms of Service or License Agreement you enter into with RMG will govern which RMG company is the controller of your data. Personal Information on this website is collected by Rural Media Group, Inc., 921 Village Square, Gretna, NE 68028, USA and its telephone number is 1-402-289-2085. Our Customer Service Department is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this privacy notice. If you have any questions, concerns, or requests about this privacy notice, how we manage your Personal Information, or any other issue relating to your Personal Information, please contact our Customer Service Department: Rural Media Group, Inc. Attn: Customer Service customerservice@rfdtv.com17445 Arbor Street; Suite 300, NE 68130Telephone number: 1-402-289-2085 http://www.rfdtv.com/category/267691/contact-us OTT Privacy Policy When using the service, RFD-TV Now processes personal data of you. The scope of the data processing is communicated in the privacy statement that may be accessed at any time within the Service. Please also note the privacy policy of our service provider Accedo for the service OTT Flow that may be accessed under the following link: www.accedo.tv/ottflow/ott-flow-privacy-policy/ Who is Cleeng? CLEENG is our trusted partner that manages our video eCommerce activities, they are a reputable expert solution in this field. Cleeng simplifies the access to unique quality content and provides great customer support. To find out more about Cleeng, please visit www.cleeng.comAboutContact UsCareersPressAffiliatesAdvertisersProgrammingSyndicationMagazineNewsletterShopAll content © copyright RFDTV.RFDTVAll Rights Reserved. For more information on this site, please read our
Privacy Policy,
Terms of Service, and
Ad Choices.
